NEHOMAH MORA

Fullstack web developer with 4 months experience specializing in object-oriented programming. I can quickly absorb new information and am always ready to learn. My greatest strength is finding alternate solutions. It enables me to find the most efficient solution while considering future impacts.

ACCOMPLISHMENTS

Learned how to code without any prior coding experience in 10 weeks.

Created individual project website.

Created a web application as a group project.

SKILLS & ABILITIES

- Utilization of PHP, mySQL, Git Version Control
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

FULLSTACK WEB DEVELOPER, DEEPDIVE CODING BOOTCAMP

12/2018 - 3/2019

Personal project was a one page site including a contact form. Group project was a dating web application. Utilized above mentioned programs to create these projects and deliver secure, efficient and aesthetically pleasing sites.

ACCOUNT EXPERT, T-MOBILE

01/2016 - 10/2018

Utilized emotional intelligence to gain the customers trust and provide a positive experience. Mentored new team members. Audited data and calls to provide resolutions on how to improve.

TECH SUPPORT, T-MOBILE

03/2011 - 01/2016

Empathizing with these customers was crucial and allowed me to be a top performer. Mentored teammates and also provided 6 months interim senior support for multiple teams.

EDUCATION

CENTRAL NEW MEXICO INGENUITY -ALBUQUERQUE, NM -CERTIFICATE

Fullstack web development certificate.